CLÉMENT HENNEBELLE

SUMMARY

After an initial career in the digital field, I chose to shift my focus by pursuing musical training, which allowed me to develop creative and technical skills. Today, I aim to restart my career in video game development by deepening my technical knowledge. With several years of experience working in digital and video game projects, I have gained solid expertise in engines such as Unity and Unreal Engine. Currently training in GLSL via Touch Designer, I am also developing skills in graphic programming. My various experiences, both in the digital field and other sectors, have allowed me to adapt to diverse environments and teams. I prioritize cohesion in group projects and place great deal of importance on the quality of the delivered work.

EDUCATION

Université de Montréal

Majeure Musiques numériques 2024

CONCORDIA UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's Computer Science 2019 Video games option

EMPLOYMENT

YISST PUB PETITE PATRIE | LEMOLIÈRE | PAMIKA THAI

Montréal, QC Déc. 2022 à En cours

BARMAN SERVER

- Jobs in service alongside my music studies
- Customer service, listening and responding to the immediate needs of clients
- Prioritization management in a fast-paced environment, prompt and efficient work

BEHAVIOUR INTERACTIVE

Montréal, QC

GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER

Juil. 2019 à Jany. 2020

- Experience with Unreal Engine 5 in C++
- Gameplay and AI programming for a networked game (handling online replication)
- Responsible for creating code modules that comply with the project's architecture, using UML, peer code review

PLAYMIND Montréal, QC

GAMEPLAY AND TECHNOLOGIES PROGRAMMER

AVR. 2018 À AOÛT 2021

- Experience with Unity 3D in C#
- Programming and handling of "real" games, with physical components that communicate with Unity
- Project management on a small programming team, and discussion with clients around the functionalities

PROJECTS

СітНив

GitHub account including projects on Unity, Unreal Engine and my portfolio website.

https://github.com/Havkiin

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES: C++, C#, GLSL, HTML / CSS, TypeScript

LANGUAGES: Français, English

SOFTWARES: Unreal Engine 5, Unity, Touch Designer, Perforce, Git

VOLUNTEERING

GANG DE DEVS (GROUPE ASSOCIATIF POUR LA NOUVELLE GÉNÉRATION DE DÉVELOPPEURS)

SEPT. 2018 À AOÛT 2021

· Administrator Montréal, QC

Organized and led monthly events with students and young professionals. Those events gave the opportunity to industry newcomers to meet veterans, and to get a better feel of life within the video game world.